

Rebecca Czilok

I am a visual designer and web developer with four years experience and a passion for all things visual. Responsibilities in previous roles included delivering a range of web applications, user journeys, managing client communications, and establishing product vision.

EXPERIENCE

Real Estate Webmasters • Vancouver

Senior Designer - JUNE 2014 - APRIL 2018

Design, Development, Project Lead and Estimating.

Freelance • Vancouver

Web Design & Illustration — OCTOBER 2013 - PRESENT

Design, Web, and Traditional Art.

EDUCATION

Centre for Arts and Technology • Kelowna

Graphic Design & Digital Multimedia − SEPTEMBER 2011 - APRIL 2013

We touched a variety of topics from Photoshop to code to branding. to illustration and print to web.

BCHLA German Exchange • Abbotsford

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JUNE 2009

I was part of an exchange program where I visited Germany for a few months in 2009. I was fully immersed in the language and culture for 3 months, along with my exchange partner who had visited me in september in the previous year.

PROJECTS

Military Home Search • Real Estate Webmasters

Web Development — OCTOBER 2015 - AUGUST 2017

Military Home Search is one of the projects I have worked on during my time with Real Estate Webmasters (REW). The work included a new home landing page, enhancing the search and listing pages, as well as creating a new dashboard experience for registered users.

web: https://www.militaryhomesearch.com/

SKILLS

Photoshop Illustrator

InDesign

HTML/CSS Javascript

CMS Management (Wordpress)

UI Design

Responsive Web Design

Project Communication

CONTACT INFORMATION

604-356-6755 rczilok@gmail.com https://lubeka.github.io/

REFERENCES

Available Upon Request





